WAVERLY WILLMAN

714 Healey Blvd, Alpine, UT · (480) 320-8058 waveyjai@gmail.com · https://www.linkedin.com/in/waverlywillman/

Highly motivated and adaptable with a diverse background in customer support and volunteer work. With a passion for assisting others, consistently improving the customer experience and fostering a positive team culture.

EXPERIENCE

AUG 2023 - CURRENT

LEAD CUSTOMER SUPPORT REPRESENTATIVE - COMMERCIAL PARTNERSHIPS, BANNER

- Utilize problem-solving skills to handle various responsibilities and tasks, supporting customers in achieving their goals and maintaining a cohesive service plan.
- Managing upsells for commercial accounts, creating contracts to address concerns found during regular maintenance, providing inbound and outbound support for large accounts.

FEB 2023 - AUG 2023

PERSONAL ASSISTANT, FAMILY CARE

Skillfully manage scheduling and time management for a busy family, ensuring smooth and efficient daily
operations.

AUG 2021 - FEB 2023

LDS MISSION, MILAN, ITALY

- Learned and achieved fluency in the Italian language.
- Cultivated values of integrity, diligence and discipline as a leader of an assigned area.
- Gained valuable experience of goal setting, putting plans into action, and following through, which continue to shape my approach to life and work.

AUG 2019 - JULY 2021

SALES ASSOCIATE, AL'S SPORTING GOODS

Improved customer experience as a cashier, attending trainings to expand product knowledge and effectively
market items to consumers.

EDUCATION

CURRENT

BACHELORS, BRIGHAM YOUNG UNIVERSITY

I am perusing a business degree in Entrepreneurship, which I hope will give me a broadened perspective on the business world and allow me to grow in experience with background and expertise.

SKILLS

- High achiever, consistently surpassing goals and delivering outstanding performance.
- Adept at giving and receiving feedback constructively, fostering a positive and collaborative work environment.
- Problem solver.
- Excellent communication skills with a talent for deescalation
- Confident in my ability to grow.

ACTIVITIES

Outside of work I enjoy being outdoors, trying new things and exploring my creativity. In the past few years I have picked up hobbies in mountain biking and climbing. I enjoy discovering new ways to enjoy nature, and even more so when I am surrounded by great friends. I pursue painting and other forms of art as a beautiful way of expression.